He can go in, see? The kitten can go in.
Ó! Ele consegue entrar. O gatinho consegue entrar.
Look.
Olha:
"For sale."
Vende.
It's all for sale.
Tudo à venda.
"For sale". The whole street is for sale.
Vende-se. A rua inteira está à venda.
All of a sudden.
De repente.
It's impressive. In 2013, the last eviction happened,
É impressionante. 2013, houve o último despejo
a real state market boom happend on the surroundings.
Houve um Boom imobiliário no entorno.
Look at this: the building has been put up at an incredible speed
Se você notar aqui, é o seguinte: Esse prédio aqui subiu em uma velocidade espantosa
And it's not the only one. There are many of them.
Mas não é o único não, vários.
So, like, this used to be a car wash... so someone bought
Então, aquela coisa. Comprou um terreno barato, aqui era um lava-rápido,
a cheap lot just waiting for things to flourish.
esperando a coisa andar.
When the population that lived here is evicted,
Então na hora que desapropria e que a população daqui é retirada
the lot becomes a prime area, "oh! there will be a cultural center!"
o terreno já valoriza: "opa! vai surgir um centro cultural!"
So they put up buildings.
E já sobe empreendimento.
You can see many signs of "for sale" there,
Alí você tem várias placas de vende-se.
which means prices have duplicated, triplicated
Quer dizer, os preços duplicaram, triplicaram
on account of having a cultural center nearby.
por conta de um centro cultural na vizinhança.